MUAZ MUHAMMAD

Patiya, Chittagong, Bangladesh ■ muazmuhammad21@gmail.com □ 01788397864 🛅 in/muaz-muhammad-ba88a3207/ ↑ https://github.com/muaz64

SUMMARY

Experienced Front-End Developer with 1 year of successful experience in developing web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and jQuery. In-depth knowledge of web design, coding practices, and user experience principles. Skilled in developing responsive websites, debugging, and optimizing for performance. Applying for a position as a Front-End Developer.

EXPERIENCE

Web designer(Front-End Developer)

Black Origin

June 2023 - Present, Chattogram

- Design user interfaces for web applications using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Develop user interfaces for web applications, usability, and cross-browser compatibility.
- $\cdot \hbox{Collaborated with the design team to implement UI/UX designs into functional web interfaces.}\\$
- · Assisted in optimizing website performance and improving accessibility.
- Review all web content and solve errors in codes.

Payroll Administrator

GMIT Institute

April 2023 - Present, Chattogram

- Processing and managing the company's payroll.
- Ensuring accurate and timely payment of employees' salaries.
- · Calculating salaries, deductions, and preparing payroll reports.
- · Tender datasheet and all sales related activities.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in EEE

International Islamic University Chittagong (IIUC) · Kumira, Chittagong

HSC

Minor in Science ⋅ South Asian College ⋅ Chattogram ⋅ 2018

SSC

Minor in Science · Hazi Mohammad Mohsin Govt. High School · Chattogram · 2016

INVOLVEMENT

Press & Publicity Secretary

International Islamic University, Chittagong • EEE Club, IIUC • January 2023 - June 2023

Assistanat Organizing Secretary-1

International Islamic University, Chittagong • EEE Club, IIUC • August 2022 - December 2022

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML,CSS,JAVASCRIPT, Microsoft Office Applications (Word, Excel, PowerPoint), Graphic Design, PLC, VFD, HMI, Matlab, NI Multisim, LTspice .